[{"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4de", "answers": [{"answer": "Equip", "id": "yvUIo", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Vacant", "id": "Swm0z", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Secure", "id": "FSrVK", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Oblige", "id": "FBvLV", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.641Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4de", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.606Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e0", "answers": [{"answer": "Effectiveness", "id": "s89sH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Accountancy", "id": "M7Ero", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Satisfaction", "id": "rWUtf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "appropriate", "id": "n4nOe", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.656Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e0", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.633Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e2", "answers": [{"answer": "weather", "id": "Lo0wv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "animal", "id": "4DWFz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "human", "id": "EnE0s", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "canteen", "id": "tOlB3", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.660Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e2", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.647Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e4", "answers": [{"answer": "familiar", "id": "8BtWH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "redundant", "id": "iLl62", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "customary", "id": "rISOR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "13ir1", "text": "reluctant", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "aFb5G", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.666Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e4", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.664Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e6", "answers": [{"answer": "forgettable", "id": "TsviI", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "philosophy", "id": "EGm9h", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "humanism", "id": "Abr2W", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "ceklr", "text": "objectively", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "61Wka", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.669Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e6", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.690Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e8", "answers": [{"answer": "referee", "id": "RXQCR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "agriculture", "id": "CVj81", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "personality", "id": "ILDT8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "aetq1", "text": "mathematics", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "PFy3K", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.673Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4e8", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.716Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ea", "answers": [{"answer": "respectable", "id": "mI7hq", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "affectionate", "id": "rat2x", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "occasional", "id": "Ntqgy", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "kindergarten", "id": "0ePaB", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.677Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ea", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.726Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ec", "answers": [{"answer": "zoology", "id": "oWJYQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "conquest", "id": "Yv1MM", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "cement", "id": "AKlp3", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "duet", "id": "Z153A", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.680Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ec", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.735Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ee", "answers": [{"answer": "photocopy", "id": "fSy5Y", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "particular", "id": "qCxXT", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "enthusiasm", "id": "TL33R", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "economy", "id": "rdp6z", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.685Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4ee", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.744Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4f0", "answers": [{"answer": "furnish", "id": "Ojly8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "reason", "id": "NWOjV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "promise", "id": "qEw2O", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "tonight", "id": "ZlJ3p", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-01T17:10:05.691Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59a9946d4a9c7f202d2df4f0", "question": "Find the words which has a different stress pattern:", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-03T14:38:22.751Z"}]